It's Gonna Get Bloody!
VFW is a action, crime, horror film directed by Joe Begos.
A typical night for veterans at a VFW turns into an all-out battle for survival
when a desperate teen runs into the bar with a bag of stolen drugs.
When a gang of violent punks come looking for her, the vets use every weapon at their
disposal to protect the girl and themselves from an unrelenting attack.
Fred, played by Stephen Lang.
Lou Clayton, played by Martin Kove.
Walter Reed, played by William Sadler.
Doug McCarthy, played by David Patrick Kelly.
Gutter, played by Dora Madison.
Lizard, played by Sierra McCormick.
VFW is a 2019 American action splatter film directed by Joe Begos and starring
Stephen Lang, William Sadler, Martin Kove and Fred Williamson.
The film premiered at the 2019 Fantastic Fest in Austin, Texas, and
released to theaters, VOD, and Digital HD on February 14, 2020.
The film explores themes of drug dealer, war veteran, gore, gang, drugs.
The tone is dark and intense.